

## **Contacts**

- **Phone** +7 (963)-747-37-32
- Telegram
  https://t.me/stpkk
- Email stipyk1309@gmail.com
- GitHub
  <a href="https://github.com/stpkkk">https://github.com/stpkkk</a>
- in LinkedIn

  www.linkedin.com/in/igorstepanov1
- Address
  Russia, Petrozavodsk

My portfolio website: https://next-js-stpkkkportfolio.vercel.app/

# **Skills**

- Next.js
- React
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Redux
- Rest API
- Styled Components
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind
- Git
- Figma
- Responsive and crossbrowser layout
- English C1 Advanced

## **IGOR STEPANOV**

#### FRONTEND-DEVELOPER

### **About Me**

 $\label{lem:continuous} A \ frontend\mbox{-} developer \ with \ experience \ in \ creating \ web \ applications \ using \ React.$ 

Good knowledge in JavaScript, TypeScript and related libraries.

Paying close attention to details, it's important for me that the code is clean, well-organized, and error-free.

Great team member, worked both in large team and as a solid developer.

Have an active life position - there are a lot of sports in my life, i love cycling and snowboarding.

Ready for full time or part time work.

Open to your suggestions and new oppotunities.

# **Experience**

#### Rukki Pro (Moscow) February 2023 - to this day

React-developer

Implementation of the interface on the stack Next.js/React/Typescript/Styled Components Joined the project at the final stage and successfully joined to team.

I successfully eliminated all interface bugs, optimized the application, at the moment I'm finishing the implementation of all business requirements and, together with the team, I am preparing the project for production.

### Technomedia (Petrozavodsk) October 2022 - February 2023

React-developer

- Worked in development of web-application "Business insurance calculator" using React, Typescript and Styled Components
- Worked in updating layouts, adding content and SEO optimization to company's main website sysdyn.ru
- Worked in development of functional components for companies projects
- Admin side development

#### Freelance December 2021 - October 2022

Frontend-developer

- Creating website layouts based in template, using HTML5 and CSS3
- Engaged in SEO optimization and website promotion
- · Design creation for websites in Figma
- Development of Adaptive and Crossbrowser layouts

# **Education**

2022 React-developer, "The way of the samurai"

it-incubator React, JavaScript, Typescript

**2021** Jonas Schmedtmann, The complete **JavaScript** Course:

Udemy From Zero to Expert

2011-2014 Management and Cadastre, Cadastral Engineer

Petrozavodsk State University